export const dataQuestions = [{
	question: '1. 5! = ?',
	answers: [
		'100',
		'120',
		'300',
		'80'
	],
	correct: '1'
}, {
	question: '2. 9 * 9 = ?',
	answers: [
		'81',
		'9',
		'63',
		'80'
	],
	correct: '0'
}, {
	question: '3. 12 * 9 = ?',
	answers: [
		'130',
		'118',
		'108',
		'98'
	],
	correct: '2'
}, {
	question: '4. 5! + 8 = ?',
	answers: [
		'118',
		'100',
		'120',
		'128'
	],
	correct: '3'
}, {
	question: '5. 8 * 7 = ?',
	answers: [
		'80',
		'68',
		'54',
		'56'
	],
	correct: '3'
}, {
	question: '6. 9 + 4 * 8 = ?',
	answers: [
		'41',
		'104',
		'50',
		'32'
	],
	correct: '0'
}, {
	question: '7. 13 * 2 = ?',
	answers: [
		'24',
		'26',
		'34',
		'21'
	],
	correct: '1'
}, {
	question: '8. 123 - 138 = ?',
	answers: [
		'15',
		'-15',
		'11',
		'19'
	],
	correct: '1'
}, {
	question: '9. 280 + 5! = ?',
	answers: [
		'389',
		'378',
		'413',
		'400'
	],
	correct: '3'
}, {
	question: '10. 834 - 235 = ?',
	answers: [
		'599',
		'630',
		'689',
		'549'
	],
	correct: '0'
}];